Eugene Durov

Digital product designer with 10+ years of all-around experience in design and a development background.

For the last several years I work in fintech in B2B and B2C. I redesigned payment forms and personal accounts, launched mobile analytics and finance applications.

Saint Petersburg +7 981 734 27 96 artewgen@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Product Designer at Tinkoff Bank

AUG 2021 – Present, Saint Petersburg

Leading the creation of the Finhealth product — a new function for the mobile bank application that provides financial rating, analytics and personal advices for improving well-being. Finhealth is an innovative product in the field of fintech.

Implementing the process of UX interviews in the company and conducted more than 50 interviews.

Product Designer at YooMoney (ex. Yandex.Money)

AUG 2019 – AUG 2021, Saint Petersburg

Responsible for the full design processes of payment solutions from the first idea to launching. During my work, I redesigned projects such as the Embedded checkout form, Redirect form and Mobile SDK. Modernization of Widget (Embedded form) is the most successful project — the conversion rate increased by more than 5% and the concept was re-used in more than 8 company projects.

Launched Yandex.Kassa mobile analytics app for for merchants.

Worked with B2C on Yandex. Fines and launched a utility bills project

Product Designer at Yandex

MAY 2019 – AUG 2019, Moscow

Participated in designing several intranet tools. Fully redesigned internal video conference service VConf, which became the most important tool for Yandex internal communication

UX/UI Designer | Frontend Developer at Personal Projects

SEP 2014 – MAY 2019, Minsk

Design and frontend development with a small team. The most successful projects:

- Web aggregator of popular Instagram profiles with a subscription to them. The service was visited by more than 150 thousand users per month and made thousands of subscriptions. During the work of service, I designed three versions of it, also engaged in frontend development (JS framework, CSS and HTML);
- Instagram account management service, which served more than a thousand profiles and worked for more than three years. I was responsible for design and frontend.

UX/UI Designer at EPAM

MAY 2011 - MAR 2014, Gomel

Worked on B2B design projects, especially on Cvent – service for group hotel reservations, that provides management, email marketing, and web surveys.

SKILLS

Product Design

Mobile and web design

User Experience

User Inteface Design

Interaction Design

Prototyping

Research

Usability testing

Design System maintainer

Wireframing

TOOLS & TECHNOLOGIES

Figma

Sketch

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe After Effects

Miro

Git

OTHER SKILLS

HTML

CSS

JS

SQL

PHP

LANGUAGES

Russian (Native)

English (B2)

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

UX/UI Design courses at IT Academy

2018-2019, Minsk

Taking courses on improving UX skills with a practicing art director. Two successfully completed projects: team and personal. The personal project Medok (mobile telemedicine service) received excellent marks.

Development courses at EPAM

2011-2012, Gomel

Completing frontend and backend courses with senior EPAM developers.

- HTML, CSS, JS;
- Java, PHP.

EDUCATION

Specialist's Degree in Software IT

2007–2012, Gomel

Francisk Skorina Gomel State University